<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> GoToSocial Documentation </title>
    <link>http://example.org/docs/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content on  GoToSocial Documentation </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/docs/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Admin Settings</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/admin/settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/admin/settings/</guid>
      <description>Admin Settings # The GoToSocial Settings interface uses the admin api routes to manage your instance. It&amp;rsquo;s combined with the User settings and uses the same OAUTH mechanism as normal clients (with scope: admin).
Account permissions # To use the Admin API your account has to be promoted as such:
./gotosocial --config-path ./config.yaml admin account promote --username YOUR_USERNAME After this, you can enter your instance domain in the login field (auto-filled if you run GoToSocial on the same domain), and login like you would with any other client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GtS CLI Tool</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/admin/cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/admin/cli/</guid>
      <description>GtS CLI Tool # GoToSocial compiles to an executable binary.
The standard way of using this binary is to run a server with the gotosocial server start command.
However, this binary can also be used as an admin tool, and for debugging.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the full output of gotosocial --help, without the big list of global config options.
GoToSocial - a fediverse social media server For help, see: https://docs.gotosocial.org. Code: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/admin/backup_and_restore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/admin/backup_and_restore/</guid>
      <description>Backup and Restore # As the GoToSocial database contains the instance as well as all user signing keys it is vital to back it up. If you lose these keys you&amp;rsquo;ll never be able to federate from this domain again. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to also encrypt your backups in order to keep the data safe at rest.
Aside from disaster recovery, there are other good reasons to keep backups. Some potential scenarios for you to consider:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
